I've been playing Delta for a long time, and I haven't encountered any ghosts. Today when Bubao was rowing in the field,
I met a very strange passerby. The game has just started, the room has a large insurance, and the bamboo bag doesn't like to search for things.
So I ran down to set up the gun. When I turned around, I found that the wild platoon passerby in trench coat had been kicked to death by a soldier.
Zhubao is ready to go up and rescue people. Mai Xiaowen, a passerby, just picked up his windbreaker and went upstairs. It was normal at this time.
Zhu Bao thought it was for safety, so he jumped into the room to save people, because there was no one nearby.
The boss thought that Mai Xiaowen had come to the rescue, so he set up his gun downstairs.
When we got downstairs, we found that Mai Xiaowen had no intention of saving people, so the chief prepared to go upstairs and save people by himself.
When Mai Xiaowen saw the owner approaching, he immediately picked up his windbreaker and refused to let me save him.
Hey, you, you, won’t you save me? The anchor didn't answer the voice inquiry, so he just refused to help. I have no idea.
It's been a stalemate like this. What are you doing? I don’t understand, it’s my first time doing wild rowing.
He put it down and I came to rescue him. Ah, you are? Didn't his insurance rob you? I don't have insurance.
So what is this for? I don't know him, I don't know. Sure enough, Delta can only play with people he knows.
There has been a stalemate here.
Or he kicked a garbage-picking Shushu to death. Shushu couldn't figure it out until he died.
Why is there a group of people in the military camp at this time? It's not serious. Put him down quickly and save him.
Don't let him lose his life! No matter what you say, you won’t answer or communicate, so I don’t care.
This is really inexplicable. It's okay, buddy, just play hard.
I'll help you take your stuff away. Ah, it's okay, I just jumped in.
There's no need for you to leave your grid to fill in supplies, I'll be fine. I'm surprised, why is this happening suddenly?
I don't know, maybe he has his own ideas. Meng Xinfeng kept urging me to leave and not to worry about him.
This kind of behavior will definitely not be tolerated by the main package. Now that I see that, I can't ignore it. No, man,
You go ahead and lick it, I'll give him the number and I'll see what he wants to do. I also want to see what he is going to do.
To be honest, I don't quite understand. I have to say that Feng Yi has a pretty good temper, even though he is like this, he still doesn’t scold him.
Here the windbreaker is specially thrown in front of the man-machine.
He probably wanted the man-machine to beat him to death, but the master looked at the right moment and a sliding shovel arrived. I can't stand it anymore,
Get this done first. What teacher are you grateful to? I thanked my brother. Let's go.
To be honest, I was disgusted by this passer-by selling a small article. How could someone be so obviously bad?
There is no experience at all in a good game, and the whole game is wasted.
After Zhu Bao rescued Windbreaker, he was not in the mood to fight and just walked away.
Veterans, please pay attention to lightning protection when encountering this ID. Remember to like and follow!